Guide to the Oregonian photographs collection circa 1850-1984
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Subjects, circa 1850-1983; circa 1910-1983; Series H
  - Politics, Subseries 18
    - Campaign Headquarters and Staffers (Box-folder 130/9)
    - Clackamas County Elections, 1981 February (Box-folder 130/10)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1928 (Box-folder 130/11)
    - Democratic National Convention, 1976 (Box-folder 130/12)
    - Elections (Box-folder 130/13)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (Box-folder 130/14)
    - International Agreements (Box-folder 130/15)
    - Mock Conventions (Box-folder 130/16)
    - Mock Elections (Box-folder 130/17)
    - Oregon State Legislature (Box-folder 130/18)
    - Presidential Inaugurations (Box-folder 130/19)
    - Repeal of the 18th Amendment (Box-folder 130/20)
      Photographs relating to the 21st Amendment, which replealed the 18th Amendment, thus ending Prohibition at the national level in the United States.
    - Republican National Committee (Box-folder 130/21)
    - Socialist Convention, 1932 (Box-folder 130/22)
    - United States Congress (Box-folder 130/23)
    - Washington State Legislature (Box-folder 130/24)
  - Porcupine-Culling Project, 1956 February (Box-folder 131/1)
    Photograph of two officials in charge of a campaign to reduce the number of porcupines in Eastern Oregon, because the animals were killing young pines in the region.
  - Public Works Committees (Box-folder 131/2)
    Photographs of development and works committee members.
  - Railroad Enthusiasts (Box-folder 131/3)
  - Railroads, Subseries 19
    - Amtrak (Box-folder 131/4)
    - Box Cars (Box-folder 131/5)
    - Caboose Cars (Box-folder 131/6)
    - Construction and Last Spike Ceremonies (Box-folder 131/7)
      See also Written Materials for a letter which refers to at least one of the images in this folder.
    - Freedom Train (Box-folder 131/8)
    - Freight Car Construction, 1950 (Box-folder 131/9)
      Series of photographs depicting freight cars being built in Omaha, Nebraska.
    - Freight Cars (Box-folder 131/10)
    - Refrigerator Cars (Box-folder 131/11)
    - Seattle, Portland & Spokane Railroad Dairy Demonstration Train, 1930 June (Box-folder 131/12)
    - Tracks, Tunnels and Trestles (Box-folder 131/13)
    - Train Accidents (Box-folder 131/14)
    - Train Interiors (Box-folder 131/15)
    - Train Safety Award Banner, 1929 April (Box-folder 131/16)
      Photograph of officials of the Oregon-Washington branch of Union Pacific Railroad accepting the banner for having the fewest accidents per employee.
    - Trains and Locomotives (1) (Box-folder 131/17)
    - Trains and Locomotives (2) (Box-folder 131/18)
    - Trains in the Dalles, 1884-1886 (Box-folder 131/19)
      Series of photographs depicting locomotives, rail yards and train tracks in the Dalles, Oregon, as well as the scene of a train accident near The Dalles.
  - Rape (Box-folder 131/20)
  - Real Estate Development (Box-folder 131/21)
  - Religious Groups and Events (1) (Box-folder 131/22)
    Photographs from a folder labeled "Religion," consisting mostly of group photographs of ministers and church organizations.
    See also: Portland - Churches & Other Houses of Worship.
  - Religious Groups and Events (2) (Box-folder 132/1)
  - Robots (Box-folder 132/2)
  - Rumrunning, 1932 March (Box-folder 132/3)
    Contains 3 mughshots of escaped convicts W. L. Kerr, C. T. Ryall, and A. S. Babcock, alleged to have been involved in liquor smuggling, as well as photograph of the raided liquor.
  - Sacco & Vanzetti Trial (1), 1927 (Box-folder 132/4)
    Trial of anarchists Nicola Sacco and Bartolomeo Vanzetti murder; both were executed. Includes photographs of demonstrations held on behalf of the two men.
  - Sacco & Vanzetti Trial (2) (Box-folder 132/5)
  - Seals (Box-folder 132/6)
  - Sediments Map (Box-folder 132/7)
    Map of Oregon showing the location of various types of sediment found in the state.
  - Senior Citizens (Box-folder 132/8)
  - Ship Jumpers (Box-folder 132/9)
  - Shipping Containers (Box-folder 132/10)
  - Sports and Recreation, Subseries 20
    - 4-Wheel Drive Races (Box-folder 132/11)
    - Airplane Races (Box-folder 132/12)
    - Archery (Box-folder 132/13)
    - Arm Wrestling (Box-folder 132/14)
    - Armadillo Races (Box-folder 132/15)
    - Auto Races (Box-folder 132/16)
    - Backpacking (Box-folder 132/17)
    - Badminton (Box-folder 132/18)
    - Baseball (Box-folder 132/19)
    - Baseball Teams (1) (Box-folder 132/20)
      Group photographs of baseball team members.
    - Baseball Teams (2) (Box-folder 132/21)
    - Basketball (Box-folder 133/1)
    - Basketball Fans, 1972-1979 (Box-folder 133/2)
      Photographs of basketball game attendees taken during and outside of games.
    - Beachcombing (Box-folder 133/3)
    - Bicycling (1) (Box-folder 133/4)
    - Bicycling (2) (Box-folder 133/5)
    - Billiards (Box-folder 133/6)
      Also known as pool.
    - Bingo (Box-folder 133/7)
    - Birdwatching (Box-folder 133/8)
    - Board Games (Box-folder 133/9)
      See also: Sports and Recreation - Checkers; Sports and Recreation - Chess.
    - Boat Races (Box-folder 133/10)
    - Bowling (Box-folder 133/11)
      Includes photographs related to lawn bowling.
    - Bridge (Box-folder 133/12)
    - Camping (Box-folder 133/13)
    - Card Games (Box-folder 133/14)
      See also: Sports and Recreation - Bridge.
    - Checkers (Box-folder 133/15)
    - Chess (Box-folder 133/16)
    - Clam-Digging (Box-folder 133/17)
    - Coaster Races (Box-folder 133/18)
    - Cock Fighting (Box-folder 133/19)
    - College Bowl (Box-folder 133/20)
    - Contests (Box-folder 134/1)
    - Crocheting (Box-folder 134/2)
    - Curling (Box-folder 134/3)
    - Darts (Box-folder 134/4)
    - Dog Races (Box-folder 134/5)
    - Dog Shows (Box-folder 134/6)
    - Dog Sled Races (Box-folder 134/7)
    - Egg Painting (Box-folder 134/8)
    - Fencing (Box-folder 134/9)
    - Fishing Derbies (Box-folder 134/10)
    - Foosball (Box-folder 134/11)
    - Football (Box-folder 134/12)
    - Frog-Jumping Contests (Box-folder 134/13)
    - Games - General (Box-folder 134/14)
      Includes photographs related to Dungeons and Dragons, Jacks, Leapfrog, and Twister.
    - Go-Cart Races (Box-folder 134/15)
    - Golf (1) (Box-folder 134/16)
    - Golf (2) (Box-folder 134/17)
    - Gymnastics and Acrobatics (Box-folder 134/18)
    - Hackey Sack (Box-folder 134/19)
    - Hand Tennis (Box-folder 134/20)
    - Handball (Box-folder 134/21)
      Includes 1946 photograph of handball team including Terry Schrunk.
    - Harness Races (Box-folder 134/22)
    - Hay Rides (Box-folder 134/23)
    - Hiking (Box-folder 134/24)
    - Hockey (Box-folder 134/25)
    - Hoose Races (Box-folder 135/1)
    - Horse Shows (1) (Box-folder 135/2)
    - Horse Shows (2) (Box-folder 135/3)
    - Horseback Riding (Box-folder 135/4)
    - Horseshoe-Throwing (Box-folder 135/5)
    - Hunting (Box-folder 135/6)
      Includes photographs from folder labeled "Hunters - Government."
    - Ice Skating (Box-folder 135/7)
    - Knitting (Box-folder 135/8)
    - Marbles Tournament, 1953 June (Box-folder 135/9)
    - Martial Arts (Box-folder 135/10)
    - Miniature Golf (Box-folder 135/11)
    - Moonwatching (Box-folder 135/12)
    - Mountain Climbing (Box-folder 135/13)
    - Parachute Jumping (Box-folder 135/14)
    - Ping Pong (Box-folder 135/15)
      Also known as table tennis.
    - Rock Hounds (Box-folder 135/16)
    - Skiing (Box-folder 135/17)
    - Soap Box Derbies (Box-folder 135/18)
    - Sports Team Captains (Box-folder 135/19)
      Group photograph taken 1923 or 1924 of basketball, football, and track team captains for the University of Oregon.
    - Swimming (Box-folder 135/20)
    - Toboggaining (Box-folder 135/21)
    - Track and Field (Box-folder 135/22)
    - Water Skiing (Box-folder 135/23)
    - Weightlifting (Box-folder 135/24)
    - Wrestling (Box-folder 135/25)
  - Spousal Abuse (Box-folder 136/1)
  - Stage Coaches (Box-folder 136/2)
  - Strikes (Box-folder 136/3)
  - Ten Commandments Plaque, 1958 (Box-folder 136/4)
    Photograph of a plaque donated to the City of Portland by the Fraternal Order of Eagles, which caused controversy due both to church-state separation arguments and the non-standard wording of commandments.
  - Timber Theft (Box-folder 136/5)
  - Tires (Box-folder 136/6)
  - Titanium (Box-folder 136/7)
  - Toys, Models, and Other Merrymaking Devices, Subseries 21
    - Boomerangs (Box-folder 136/8)
    - Dolls (1) (Box-folder 136/9)
    - Dolls (2) (Box-folder 136/10)
    - Dollhouses and Furniture (Box-folder 136/11)
    - Figurines and Miniatures (Box-folder 136/12)
    - Frisbees (Box-folder 136/13)
    - Hula Hoops (Box-folder 136/14)
    - Jump Rope (Box-folder 136/15)
    - Kites (Box-folder 136/16)
    - Miniature Battlefields (Box-folder 136/17)
    - Miniature Circus (Box-folder 136/18)
    - Miniature Houses (Box-folder 136/19)
    - Model Airplanes (Box-folder 136/20)
    - Model Bridges (Box-folder 136/21)
    - Model Cars (Box-folder 136/22)
    - Model Rockets (Box-folder 136/23)
    - Model Ships and Boats (Box-folder 137/1)
    - Model Tractors (Box-folder 137/2)
    - Model Trains and Railroads (Box-folder 137/3)
    - Model Wagons (Box-folder 137/4)
    - Teddy Bears (Box-folder 137/5)
    - Toy Cannons (Box-folder 137/6)
  - Traffic Signs (Box-folder 137/7)
  - Train Robbery (Box-folder 137/8)
    Photographs of suspects and victims of train robberies.
  - Trophies (Box-folder 137/9)
  - Typewriters (Box-folder 137/10)
  - Undocumented Immigrants (Box-folder 137/11)
    Originally filed as "Aliens" and "Illegal Aliens."
  - United States Constitution (Box-folder 137/12)
  - United States Constitution Sequencentennial Celebration, 1937 (Box-folder 137/13)
    Contains photograph of a certificate given to Lipman, Wolfe & Co. for its participation in the celebration.
  - United States Revolution Bicentennial Celebrations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 137/14)
  - Vacuum Cleaners (Box-folder 137/15)
  - Weather and Seasons, Subseries 22
    - Autumn (Box-folder 137/16)
      Also known as Fall.
    - Drought (Box-folder 137/17)
    - Dust Storms (Box-folder 137/18)
    - Fog (Box-folder 137/19)
      Includes photographs related to fog-seeding experiments and fog-dispersal attempts.
    - Frost (Box-folder 137/20)
    - Hail (Box-folder 137/21)
    - Ice (Box-folder 137/22)
    - Lightning (Box-folder 137/23)
    - Snow (Box-folder 137/24)
      Contains photograph of unnamed creek in the Cascade foothills during snowy weather.
  - Wireless Radios (Box-folder 137/25)
  - World Federalist Congress, 1965 June (Box-folder 137/26)
- Oversize A, 1916-1984; Series I
  Oversize images up to 11 by 14 inches.
  - People - A-G (Box-folder 138/1)
  - People - H-M (Box-folder 138/2)
  - People - N-Z (Box-folder 138/3)
  - Oregon, Subseries 1
    - 4-H Club; Adair Air Force Base; Agate Beach; Albany Timber Carnival; Ashland (Box-folder 138/4)
    - Astoria; Aurora; Mt. Bachelor; Bandon; Bayocean Peninsula; Beaver Boys State; Beaverton; Bend (Box-folder 138/5)
    - Black Butte; Blue Lake Regional Park; Boiler Bay State Park; Boy Scouts (Box-folder 138/6)
    - Bridges; Broken Top (Box-folder 138/7)
    - Bull Run Watershed; Burns (Box-folder 138/8)
      Includes photograph of Frank B. Cohen's residence west of Portland and photographs of Oregon State University.
    - Camp Clark; Camp Colton; Camp Fire Girls; Camp Hancock; Camp Howard; Camp Ma-Ku-Ala; Camp Namanu; Camp Rilea (Box-folder 138/9)
    - Cannon Beach; Cascade Head; Cascade Locks; Cedar Hills; Celilo Falls; Central Oregon (Box-folder 138/10)
    - Christmas Celebrations; Clackamas County; Clackamas County Fair; Clackamas River; Clackamas Town Center (Box-folder 138/11)
    - Clifton; Cohen Home; Columbia River; Corvallis; Crag Rats; Crane Prairie Reservoir (Box-folder 138/12)
    - Dabney State Park; Dams (Box-folder 138/13)
    - Delake; Demonstrations; Depoe Bay; Dundee (Box-folder 138/14)
    - Easter Celebrations; Estacada Timber Fair; Eugene; Explorer Scouts (Box-folder 138/15)
    - Fires (1) (Box-folder 139/1)
    - Fires (2) (Box-folder 139/2)
    - Fires (3) (Box-folder 139/3)
    - Fires (4) (Box-folder 139/4)
    - Floods (1) (Box-folder 139/5)
    - Floods (2) (Box-folder 139/6)
    - Floods (3); Florence (Box-folder 139/7)
    - Forest Fires (Box-folder 139/8)
    - Forest Grove - Stimson Lumber Co.; Fort Stevens; Fossil; Frenchglen; Gaston; Gifford Pinchot National Forest; Gilchrist; Gladstone; Granite (Box-folder 139/9)
    - Grants Pass; Gresham; Hagg Lake; Halloween Celebrations; Hay Creek Ranch; Highways (Box-folder 139/10)
      Contains photographs of the Jenkins Estate below Cooper Mountain.
    - Hillsboro; Hillsboro Airport (Box-folder 139/11)
    - Mt. Hood (1) (Box-folder 139/12)
    - Mt. Hood (2), 1970 (Box-folder 139/13)
      Contains maps of areas along the Oregon coast affected by proposed restrictions on driving on the beach
    - Hood River; Jenkins Home; Joseph - Chief Jospeh Days; Kidnappings; King City; Kiwanis Club (Box-folder 139/14)
    - Klamath Falls; Klamath Indian Reservation; Lake Oswego; Lakeview; Landslides; Lincoln City; Lost Forest Dune Park (Box-folder 139/15)
    - Malheur Wildlife Refuge; McKenzie River; Mt. McLoughlin; Memlaoose Island; Lake Merwin; Milwaukie; Mist; Mt. Angel; Multnomah; Multnomah Falls; Murders; Oak Grove; Open Aire Faire (Box-folder 139/16)
    - Oregon State Highway Commission Maps (Box-folder 139/17)
    - Pendleton - Eastern Oregon Hospital & Training Center; Rogue River; Rooster Rock; St. Paul; Salem (Box-folder 140/1)
    - Sheridan; Sherwood; Silverton; Tigard; Tillamook Bay; Tongue Point Naval Base; Troutdale; Tualitin Mountains (Box-folder 140/2)
    - Vanport; Wallowa Mountains; Washington County Crime Rate Chart (1971); West Union (Box-folder 140/3)
  - Portland, Subseries 2
    - 200 Market Building; 4-H Club; 5th Street; A. A. Horsfelot Building; Alpenrose Dairy; Albina District (Box-folder 140/4)
    - Albertina Kerr Nursery; American Legion Convention (1970) (Box-folder 140/5)
    - Apartments (Box-folder 140/6)
      Includes images of Ambassador Apartments, Astro Apartments, Clay Towers, Four Oaks Apartments, Evergreen Apartments Grant Tower, Ione Plaza, King Tower, Lincoln Tower, McCormick Pier Apartments, Portland Center Apartments, Tudor Arms, and Unthank Plaza.
    - April Fool's Day Celebrations; Arbor Day Celebrations; Artquake; Arts & Crafts Society (Box-folder 140/7)
    - Banks; Barber Block (Box-folder 140/8)
    - Barker Manufacturing Co.; Battleship Oregon Park; Black United Front; Blue Birds; Bombings; Boy Scouts; Broadmoor Golf Course (Box-folder 140/9)
    - Bridges (1) (Box-folder 140/10)
    - Bridges (2) (Box-folder 140/11)
    - Fremont Bridge (Box-folder 140/12)
    - I-205 Bridge (Box-folder 140/13)
      Also known as the Glen Jackson Bridge
    - Building Size Comparison Chart, 1976 (Box-folder 140/14)
    - Bumble Bee Inc.; Burnside Trolley Building; Bus Lane Map (1976); Carillon Center Condominium; Cascade Runoff (Box-folder 140/15)
    - Cathedral Park; The Children's Club Day Care Center; Children's Museum; Chinatown District; Christmas Celebrations (Box-folder 141/1)
    - Churches and Other Houses of Worship (1) (Box-folder 141/2)
    - Churches and Other Houses of Worship (2) (Box-folder 141/3)
    - City-County Civic Center; City-County Kelly Butte Communication Center; City Flag Design (1969); Clair Arrow Center for Women Prisoners; Clyde Cosby Trial (1957); The Colony; Columbia Slough; Congress of Industrial Organizations (CIO) Convention (1948); Commonwealth Building; Contact Center (Box-folder 141/4)
    - Container Corp. of America; Continental Motel; Couch Park; Council Crest; Country Fair; Country Store; Cub Scouts; Cultura d'Italia (Box-folder 141/5)
    - Daughters of Neptune; David Campbell Memorial Fountain; Dekum Building; Delta Park; Demonstrations (1) (Box-folder 141/6)
    - Demonstrations (2) (Box-folder 141/7)
    - Department of Human Services Multi-Service Center; Disaster Drills; Donald E. Long Juvenile Home; Downtown Athletic Club; Duniway Center; Duniway Park; Eagle Scouts; Eastbank Esplanade (Box-folder 141/8)
    - Easter Celebrations (Box-folder 141/9)
    - Education Service Center; Emergency Services; Episcopal Convention (1922); Equitable Building; Equitable Savings & Loan Association; Evans Products Co. (Box-folder 141/10)
    - Explosions; Exposition-Recreation Commission; FMC Corp.; Fairytale Parade; Family Fair; Federal Building; Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) Offices; Fire Department (Box-folder 141/11)
    - Festival Center, 1964 (Box-folder 141/12)
      Series of conceptual drawings for a proposed "Festival Center."
    - Fires (1) (Box-folder 141/13)
    - Fires (2) (Box-folder 141/14)
    - Fires (3) (Box-folder 141/15)
    - Fires (4) (Box-folder 142/1)
    - Fires (5) (Box-folder 142/2)
    - Fires (6) (Box-folder 142/3)
    - Fires (7) (Box-folder 142/4)
    - Fires (8) (Box-folder 142/5)
    - Floods; Forest Park; Fountain Gallery; Fountain Plaza (Box-folder 142/6)
    - Fountains (Box-folder 142/7)
    - Fred Meyer, Inc.; Fred N. Bay News Co.; Fruit & Flower Day Nursery; Gabirel Park; Galleria; Georgia-Pacific Building; Glaser Bros. Distribution Center; Goodwill Industries (Box-folder 142/8)
    - Grant Bowl; Green Home; Greenfingers Project; Greyhound Van Lines; Gunderson Brothers Engineering Corp.; Halloween Celebrations (Box-folder 142/9)
    - Harbor; Hare Krishna; Harney Marina Co.; Highland Games; Jike for Hungry (1971 May); Hostage Situations (Box-folder 142/10)
    - Hospitals and Clinics (1) (Box-folder 142/11)
      Includes images of: Doernbecher Memorial Hospital; Emmanuel Hospital; Good Samaritan Hospital; Living Rehabilitation Center; Medical Arts Building; Multnomah County Hospital; Oregon Health & Science University (labeled as University of Oregon Medical Hospital); Providence Hospital; St. Vincent Hospital; Shriner's Hospital; Veterans Hospital.
    - Hospitals and Clinics (2) (Box-folder 142/12)
    - Hotels (Box-folder 142/13)
      Includes images of Benson Hotel, Congress Hotel, Estate Hotel, Foster Hotel, Freeway Hotel, Hilton Hotel, Holiday Inn, Hoyt Hotel, Lenox Hotel, Lloyd Hotel, Lotus Hotel, Maraba West Hotel, Marriott Hotel, Merchants Hotel; Park Haviland Hotel, Taylor Hotel, and West Hotel.
    - Housing Survey (1949); Hoyt Arboretum; Hudson Sales Corp.; Hughes Building; Independence Day Celebrations; Indian Guides; Indochinese Cultural & Service Center; Iris Court Day Care Center (Box-folder 142/14)
    - J. K. Gill Co. Warehouse (Box-folder 142/15)
      Map on black paper. Only item in folder for preservation reasons.
    - Jailbreaks; Japanese Culture Festival; Jefferson High School; Jewish Community Center; Job's Daughters; Johns Landing; Junior League; Justice Center; Juvenile Detention Home; KBPS Radio Station; Kelly Home; Kidnappings (Box-folder 142/16)
      Includes an images of the Clinton Kelly residence.
    - Labor Day Celebrations; Laubach Literacy, Inc.; Laurelhurst Park; Leauge of Women Voters; Lents District; Leupold & Stevens Instruments, Inc.; Libraries (Box-folder 143/1)
    - Lincoln Building; Lincoln Memorial Park; Lloyd Center; Lloyd Tower; March of Dimes (Box-folder 143/2)
    - Maps of Downtown District, 1978 (Box-folder 143/3)
      Two images showing the locations of prominent buildings in downtown Portland.
    - Meier & Frank; Memorial Coliseum; Memorial Day Celebrations (Box-folder 143/4)
    - Methodist Conference (1976 April); Moore Lithograph & Mailings Co., Inc.; Morrison Center for Youth & Family Services; Mt. Scott Community Center; Mt. Tabor Reservoir; Multnomah County Animal Control; Multnomah County Commission; Multnomah County Court Case Closure Graph (1971); Multnomah County Courthouse; Multnomah County Fair (Box-folder 143/5)
    - Multnomah Countuy Juvenile Court; Multnomah County Juvenile Home; Multnomah County Morgue; Multnomah Golf Club; Murders; National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Convention (1978); Naturalization Ceremonies; Northwest Food Fair; One Main Place; Operation Clean Sweep (1975) (Box-folder 143/6)
    - Orbanco Building; Oregonian Jubilee Celebration (1925); Pacific First Federal Center; Pacific International Livestock Exposition Center; Pacific Northwest Bell; Pedestrian Mall; Personal Car Center; Police Department; Police Department - Sunshine Division (Box-folder 143/7)
    - Portarbour Condominiums; Portland Art Museum; Portland Building; Portland Plaza Condominiums (Box-folder 143/8)
    - Portland Rose Festival (Box-folder 143/9)
    - Portland Union Stockyards Co.; Poulsen Home; Powell Grove Cemetery; Project Second Wind; Pythian Building; Public Market Building; Public Service Builing Purse-Snatching Rates Graph (1971); Rape (Box-folder 143/10)
      The Public Market Building sevred as the Oregon Journal's Offices from 1948 to 1961.
    - Refugees; Reid Home; Ross Island Grocery Store; Russell & Blythe Building; St. Johns Day Care Center; St. Vincent de Paul's Day Care Center; Sanctuary of Our Sorrowful Mother; South End Grocery Store; Southwest Multnomah Mutli-Use Center; State Office Building (Box-folder 143/11)
      Includes images of Vanport Flood refugees and Hungarian refugees.
    - Statues; Stevens Building; The Storage Place; Swan Island; Thanksgiving Celebrations (Box-folder 143/12)
    - Thomas E. Mahoney Tria (1957); Tri-Met; United States District Court; Urban Renewal (Box-folder 143/13)
    - US Bancorp Tower; US Bank Plaza; Views; Walk for the Third World (1971) Washington Park - Japanese Gardens; Washington Park Zoo (1) (Box-folder 143/14)
    - Washington Park Zoo (2) (Box-folder 143/15)
    - Waverly Country Club; Wildlife Rehabilitation Center; Willamette River; Willamette Iron & Steel Works; World Trade Center (Box-folder 143/16)
      World Trade Center is also known as Willamette Center.
  - Washington State (1) (Box-folder 144/1)
  - Washington State (2) (Box-folder 144/2)
  - Washington State (3) (Box-folder 144/3)
  - Washington State (4) (Box-folder 144/4)
  - Washington State (5) (Box-folder 144/5)
  - Washington State - Mt. St. Helens (Box-folder 144/6)
    Includes images before the 1980 eruption and images from 1981 to 1984.
  - Washington State - Mt. St. Helens Eruption, 1980 (Box-folder 144/7)
    Includes images taken in the months following the eruption.
  - Other US Locations (Box-folder 144/8)
  - Non-US Locations - Canada, Mexico (Box-folder 144/9)
  - Accidents; Adoption; Agriculture (1) (Box-folder 144/10)
  - Agriculture (2) (Box-folder 144/11)
  - Agriculture (3) (Box-folder 144/12)
  - Agriculture (4) (Box-folder 144/13)
  - Agriculture (5) (Box-folder 144/14)
  - Alleys; Amish People; Antiques; Archaeology (Box-folder 144/15)
  - Art (1) (Box-folder 145/1)
  - Art (2) (Box-folder 145/2)
  - Art (3) (Box-folder 145/3)
  - Steamboat Creek Sketch, 1947 July 10 (Box-folder 145/4)
    Original pencil sketch by Peter Winthrop Sheffers during trip in Umpqua River Region; reproduced in issue for August 31 1947 issue.
    Only image in folder for preservation purposes.
  - Auctions (Box-folder 145/5)
  - Aviation (1) (Box-folder 145/6)
  - Aviation (2) (Box-folder 145/7)
  - Aviation (3) (Box-folder 145/8)
  - Aviation (4) (Box-folder 145/9)
  - Aviation (5) (Box-folder 145/10)
  - Babies; Babysitting; Balloons; Bank Robberies; Bathrooms; Bazaars; Bicycle Accidents; Bicycles (Box-folder 145/11)
  - Billboards; Birthday Celebrations; Blackouts; Blacksmiths; Blind People; Block Home Program (Box-folder 145/12)
  - Boats and Other Watercraft (1) (Box-folder 145/13)
  - Boats and Other Watercraft (2) (Box-folder 145/14)
  - Boats and Other Watercraft (3) (Box-folder 145/15)
  - Boats and Other Watercraft (4) (Box-folder 145/16)